A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Soviet Studies, Record Group 3, Series 6 FA1486
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Fellowship Records and Institutional Support, 1985-1995; 2
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Slezkine, Yuri, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 559)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Steinberg, Mark, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 560)
  - Graduate Training - Andrews, Josephine, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 561)
  - Graduate Training - Barris, Roann, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 562)
  - Graduate Training - Cassiday, Julie, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 563)
  - Graduate Training - Chavin, James, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 564)
  - Graduate Training - Cohen, Shari, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 565)
  - Graduate Training - Cohen, Shari, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 565 A)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2031.
  - Graduate Training - Frank, Allen, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 566)
  - Graduate Training - Goldman, Philip, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 567)
  - Graduate Training - Goldman, Philip, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 567 A)
  - Graduate Training - Kahn, Andrew, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 568)
  - Graduate Training - Neuhauser, Kimberly, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 569)
  - Graduate Training - Nevitt, Christopher, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 570)
  - Graduate Training - Platz, Stephanie, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 571)
  - Graduate Training - Rossman, Jeffrey, 1991 (Box 53, Folder 572)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Ament, Suzanne, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 573)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Bisha, Robin, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 574)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Darst, Robert, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 575)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Darst, Robert, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 575 A)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Dawson, Jane, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 576)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Dawson, Jane, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 576 A)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Gaudin, Corinne, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 577)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Hellman, Joel, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 578)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Kotsonis, John, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 579)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Morrissey, Susan, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 580)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Nelson, Amy, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 581)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Paine, Sarah, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 582)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Pevny, Olenka, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 583)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Poe, Marshall, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 584)
    File consists of a letter from Poe, declining the SSRC award, as he had also received an IREX grant.
    The document was misfiled at the end of another fellow's file.
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Presto, Jenifer, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 585)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Trail, Matthew, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 586)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Trail, Matthew, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 586 A)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Twigg, Judyth, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 587)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Danielian, Lucig, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 588)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Danielian, Lucig, 1991 (Box 54, Folder 588 A)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Frank, Stephen, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 589)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Kiernan, Brendan, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 590)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Kornblatt, Judith, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 591)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - May, Rachel, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 592)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Ruttenburg, Nancy, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 593)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Shearer, David, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 594)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Slay, Ben, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 595)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Weathersby, Kathryn, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 596)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Reviewer Comments, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 589 A - 596 A)
    Related Materials
    Reviewer comments removed from folders 589-596, for Stephen Frank, Brendan Kiernan, Judith Kornblatt, Rachel May, Nancy Ruttenburg, David Shearer, Ben Slay, and Kathryn Weathersby.
  - Graduate Training - Bell, James, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 597)
  - Graduate Training - Blitstein, Peter, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 598)
  - Graduate Training - Frye, Timothy, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 599)
  - Graduate Training - Gerber, Theodore, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 600)
  - Graduate Training - King, Charles, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 601)
  - Graduate Training - Martin, Virginia, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 602)
  - Graduate Training - Prokop, Jane, 1992 (Box 55, Folder 603)
  - Graduate Training - Smyth, Regina, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 604)
  - Graduate Training - Taylor, Brian, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 605)
  - Graduate Training - Werner, Cynthia, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 606)
  - Graduate Training - Wimberg, Ellen, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 607)
  - Graduate Training - Woodruff, David, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 608)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Dudwick, Nora, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 609)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Fenander, Sara, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 610)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Garcelon, Marc, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 611)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Geraci, Robert, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 612)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Helf, Gavin, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 613)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Jersild, Austin, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 614)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Kennedy, Craig, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 615)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - King, Tracy, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 616)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Mendelson, Sarah, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 617)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Nathans, Benjamin, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 618)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Petrone, Karen, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 619)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Petrone, Karen, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 619 A)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2032.
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Shevsov, Vera, 1992 (Box 56, Folder 620)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Smidchens, Guntis, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 621)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Smith, Kathleen, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 622)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Burds, Jeffrey, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 623)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Forrester, Sibelan, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 624)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Goldberg, Linda, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 625)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Koblitz, Ann, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 626)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Kotkin, Stephen, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 627)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Naiman, Eric, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 628)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Smith, Michael, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 629)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Wegren, Stephen, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 630)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Reviewer Comments, 1992 (Box 57, Folder 623 A - 630 A)
    Reviewer comments removed from folders 623-630, for Jeffrey Burds, Sibelan Forrester, Linda Goldberg, Ann Koblitz, Stephen Kotkin, Eric Naiman, Michael Smith, and Stephen Wegren.
  - Graduate Training - Buyske, Gail, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 631)
  - Graduate Training - Cahn, Jennifer, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 632)
  - Graduate Training - Ely, Christopher, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 633)
  - Graduate Training - Johnson, Juliet, 1993 (Box 57, Folder 634)
  - Graduate Training - Kuenzi, David, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 635)
  - Graduate Training - Liu, Morgan, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 636)
  - Graduate Training - Petryna, Adriana, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 637)
  - Graduate Training - Quimby, Peter, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 638)
  - Graduate Training - Ranjbaran, Guita, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 639)
  - Graduate Training - Rosenblatt, Delia, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 640)
  - Graduate Training - Tyson, David, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 641)
  - Graduate Training - Werning, Sharon, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 642)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Barris, Roann, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 643)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Foglesong, Todd, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 644)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Gorham, Michael, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 645)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Herman, Robert, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 646)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Kahn, Daniel, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 647)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Lemon, Alaina, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 648)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Manchester, Laurie, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 649)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Marrese, Michelle, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 650)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Mogul, Jonathan, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 651)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Sedaitis, Judith, 1993 (Box 58, Folder 652)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Sherlock, Wallace, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 653)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Slepyan, Kenneth, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 654)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Weiner, Adam, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 655)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Cavanagh, Clare, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 656)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Gasparetti, David, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 657)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Hellman, Joel, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 658)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Kaiser, Robert, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 659)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Lehmann, Susan, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 660)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Levin, Theodore, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 661)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Robson, Roy, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 662)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Spagat, Michael, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 663)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Sharp, Jane, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 664)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Thyret, Isolde, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 665)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Wolff, David, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 666)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Reviewer Comments, 1993 (Box 59, Folder 656 A - 666 A)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2033.
    Reviewer comments removed from folders 656-666, for Clare Cavanagh, David Gasperetti, Joel Hellman, Robert Kaiser, Susan Lehmann, Theodore Levin, Roy Robson, Jane Sharp, Michael Spagat, Isolde Thyret, and David Wolff.
  - Graduate Training - Brown, Kathryn, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 667)
  - Graduate Training - Carlisle, Heather, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 668)
  - Graduate Training - Goluboff, Sascha, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 669)
  - Graduate Training - Graney, Katherine, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 670)
  - Graduate Training - Senick-Goldstein, Jennifer, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 671)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Alexopoulos, Golfo, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 672)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Essig, Laurie, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 673)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Frye, Timothy, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 674)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Hessler, Julie, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 675)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Jacobson, Lester, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 676)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Kiaer, Christina, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 677)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Moser, Robert, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 678)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Nevitt, Christopher, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 679)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Pannell, Kerry, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 680)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Penner, D'Ann (D'Ann Rook), 1994 (Box 60, Folder 681)
    D'Ann Rook's name changed to Penner in July 1994.
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Platz, Stephanie, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 682)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Reddaway, Darlene, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 683)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Sunderland, Willard, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 684)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Tuminez, Astrid, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 685)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - West, Sally, 1994 (Box 60, Folder 686)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Buckley, Cynthia, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 687)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Ciepiela, Catherine, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 688)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Crowley, Stephen Fitzgerald, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 689)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Gheith, Jehanne, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 690)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Mitchneck, Beth, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 691)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Moeller-Sally, Stephen, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 692)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Ries, Nancy, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 693)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Schoeberlein-Engel, John Samuel, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 694)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Solnick, Steven, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 695)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Weeks, Theodore, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 696)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Reviewer Comments, 1994 (Box 61, Folder 687 A - 696 A)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2034.
    Reviewer sheets removed from folders 687-696, for Cynthia Buckley, Catherine Ciepiela, Stephen Crowley, Jehanne Gheith, Beth Mitchneck, Stephen Moeller-Sally, Nancy Ries, John Schoeberlein-Engel, Steven Solnick, and Theodore Weeks.
  - Graduate Training - Edgar, Adrienne (Turkmenistan), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1788)
  - Graduate Training - Kenworthy, Scott M. (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1789)
  - Graduate Training - King, Alexander D. (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1790)
  - Graduate Training - L'Heureux, Marie Alice (Estonia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1791)
  - Graduate Training - MacFarquhar, Rory (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1792)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Kalinowska-Blackwood, Izabela (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1793)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Kuehnast Rasmussen, Kathleen (Kyrgyzstan), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1794)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Luong, Pauline Jones (Uzbekistan), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1795)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Martin, Russell E. (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1796)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - O'Neil, Catherine (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1797)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Park, Lynda Yoon-Sun (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1798)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Schrader, Abby M. (Russia), 1995 (Box 111, Folder 1799)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Sperling, Valerie (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1800)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Spock, Jennifer B. (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1801)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Wanner, Catherine (Ukraine), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1802)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Weinthal, Erika (Uzbekistan), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1803)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Werner, Cynthia Ann (Kazakhstan), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1804)
  - Dissertation Fellowships - Werth, Paul William (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1805)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Fish, M. Steven (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1806)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Fowler, George (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1807)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Gorsuch, Anne (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1808)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Hendley, Kathryn (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1809)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Kizenko, Nadieszda (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1810)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Kotsonis, Yanni (Russia), 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1811)
  - Postdoctoral Fellowships - Reviewer Comments, 1995 (Box 112, Folder 1806 A - 1811 A)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2035.
    Reviewer comments removed from folders 1806-1811, for M. Steven Fish, George Fowler, Anne Gorsuch, Kathryn Hendley, Nadieszda Kizenko, and Yanni Kotsonis.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program, 1985 (Box 131, Folder 2068)
    Proposal by John Stremlau for a Rockefeller Foundation-funded International Fellowship Program on Soviet International Behavior (subsequently, International Fellowship Program for the Development of Soviet Studies).
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program (3 folders), 1986 (Box 131, Folder 2069 - 2071)
    Planning meeting, March 1986; Herbert Ellison report, May 1986; planning group meeting, November 10, 1986.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Design Study (Herbert Ellison), 1986 (Box 131, Folder 2072)
    Ellison was hired as a consultant. Report, May 1986.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Correspondence with John Coatsworth, 1986-1987 (Box 131, Folder 2073)
    Coatsworth was chair of the Joint Committee on Latin American Studies.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 2074)
    Selection panel meeting, June 1, 1987; program report, July 1, 1987.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 2074 A)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 2075)
    Selection panel meeting, June 2, 1988; program report, September 1, 1988.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 2075 A)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2028.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Award Letters and Declinations, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 2076)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 2077)
    Selection panel meeting, June 12, 1989; program report, September 1, 1989.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program, 1989 (Box 132, Folder 2077 A)
    Restricted - Peer Review - Open in 2029.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Panel Members, 1985-1989 (Box 132, Folder 2078)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Announcements and Mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 132, Folder 2079)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Applicants, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 2080)
    Requests for applications, nominations, and submissions.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Budget, 1986-1990 (Box 132, Folder 2081)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - General, 1989-1991 (Box 61, Folder 697)
    International Fellowship Program for the Development of Soviet Studies. Program was funded by the Rockefeller Foundation.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Abebe, Ermias, 1987-1989 (Box 61, Folder 698)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Banerjee, Jyotirmoy, 1987-1990 (Box 61, Folder 699)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Cerdas-Cruz, Rodolfo, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 700)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Hussain, Farhat, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 701)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Banerjee, Geetasree, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 702)
    File consists of application form and covering letter, which were misfiled in Jyotirmoy Banerjee file (no apparent relation).
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Capelli, Ottorino, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 703)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Devlet, Nadir, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 704)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Grancelli, Bruno, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 705)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Jayawardane, Sri Amal, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 706)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Mondry, Henrietta, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 707)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Narayanswamy, Ramnath, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 708)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Patula, Jan, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 709)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Romero, Carlos, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 710)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Sheikh, Ali, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 711)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Taha, Taha Abdel-Alim, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 712)
    Full name variously: Taha Abdel Aleem Taha (or Taha Adam).
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Tuminez, Astrid, 1988-1990 (Box 63, Folder 713)
    Full name, Mary Astrid Tuminez.
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Balogun, F. Odun, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 714)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Bhattacharya, Abhijit, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 715)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Dash, Padma, 1989-1991 (Box 63, Folder 716)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Khaddar, Moncef, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 717)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Nascimento, Paulo C., 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 718)
  - JCSS - International Fellowship Program - Rais, Rasul Bux, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 719)
  - Summer Language Institutes, 1985 (Box 130, Folder 2060-2061)
    Includes selection panel meetings, April 26, 1985, and November 1, 1985. Grant amendment, August - September 1985, provided an additional $50,000 to support training in the non-Russian languages of the Soviet Union.
  - Summer Language Institutes, 1986 (Box 130, Folder 2062-2063)
    Includes selection panel meeting, February 14, 1986.
  - Summer Language Institutes, 1987 (Box 130, Folder 2064-2065)
    Selection panel meeting, February 27, 1987.
  - Summer Language Institutes - Reports, 1987 (Box 131, Folder 2066)
  - Summer Language Institutes, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 2067)
    Selection panel meeting, February 6, 1988.
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Bryn Mawr College, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 720)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Indiana University, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 721)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS), 1990 (Box 63, Folder 722)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Middlebury College, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 723)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Monterey Institute, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 724)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Norwich University, 1990 (Box 63, Folder 725)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Harvard University, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 726)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Georgian - Indiana University, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 727)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - Indiana University, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 728)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1990 (Box 64, Folder 729)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - University of Washington, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 730)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Beloit College, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 731)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Bryn Mawr Colege, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 732)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Indiana University, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 733)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advance International Studies (SAIS), 1991 (Box 64, Folder 734)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Middlebury College, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 735)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Monterey Institute, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 736)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Monterey Institute, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 736 A)
    Restricted - Student records - Open in 2066.
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Norwich University, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 737)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Harvard University, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 738)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Georgian - Indiana University, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 739)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - Indiana University, 1991 (Box 64, Folder 740)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek and Azeri - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1991 (Box 65, Folder 741)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh - University of Washington, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 742)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Tajik - University of Washington, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 743)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek - University of Washington, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 744)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh, Kazan Tatar - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 745)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Beloit College, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 746)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Bryn Mawr College, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 747)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Indiana University, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 748)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Johns Hopkins University, School of Advanced International Studies (SAIS), 1992 (Box 65, Folder 749)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Middlebury College, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 750)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Monterey Institute, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 751)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - Norwich University, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 752)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Russian - University of Iowa, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 753)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Ukrainian - Harvard University, 1992 (Box 65, Folder 754)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Georgian and Uzbek - Indiana University, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 755)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Uzbek, Azeri - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1992 (Box 66, Folder 756)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh, Tajik, and Uzbek - University of Washington, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 757)
  - Summer Language Institutes - Kazakh and Kazan Tatar - University of Wisconsin-Madison, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 758)